For this quiz, I want you to do a little bit of research.
Neste teste, quero que você faça um pouco de pesquisa.
I'm giving you a link, below, to the Mozilla Developer Network.
Estou dando um link, abaixo, para o Mozilla Developer Network.
It has an HTML element reference that is a super useful tool for
Ele tem uma referência de elemento HTML que é uma ferramenta superútil para
every web developer.
todo desenvolvedor Web.
In fact, I encourage you to use Mozilla Developer Network whenever you want to
De fato, recomendo usar o Mozilla Developer Network sempre que quiser
look something up.
pesquisar alguma coisa.
In fact, I want you to practice now.
Agora, quero que você pratique.
I'm going to give you this html.
Vou te dar este HTML.
I want you to search for bold in emphasis, over here, in your browser.
Quero que você pesquise bold (negrito) e emphasis (ênfase), bem aqui, no seu navegador.
Just use the find function, which is either going to be a Cmd f or Ctrl f.
Basta usar a função Find (Localizar), que pode ser Cmd f ou Ctrl f.
And then once you've found out how to make something bold or
E, quando descobrir como colocar negrito ou
emphasize it, do that over here.
ênfase, faça isso bem aqui.
Make this text bold and then emphasize this text.
Coloque este texto em negrito e, depois, enfatize este texto.
Good luck.
Boa sorte.
I know that you can do it.
Eu sei que você consegue.